RENATA ZBIEĆ - PIEKARSKA

r.zbiec.piekarska@gmail.com

ABOUT ME I am a meticulous and diligent quick learner, ready for hard work and developing professional skills in IT areas. My inner driving force is continuous development. I like to learn new things and share knowledge and experience gained so far. I truly believe that team working is the key to success. Thanks to participating in the workshops and courses on the basics of programming (Javascript, CSS, HTML), I gained confidence that this is the direction I would like to develop. I like new challenges and gaining new skills gives me personal satisfaction.

EDUCATION

Warsaw University of Life Science	Warsaw Medical University	Kozminsky University
M.Sc. Eng. in Biotechnology	PhD in medical sciences	Postgraduate Programs "R&D projects managments and commercialization"
1997 - 2002	2011	2012 - 2013

EXPERIENCE

R&D Project manager

2013 - present

Central Forensic Laboratory of the Police

Responsible for the management of several R&D projects:

- Created action plans and timelines
- Established goals, roles, and responsibilities
- Effectively interact with other departments and organizations
- Organized and managed project teams which involved fostering collaborations, convening and facilitating meetings
- Supervising IT teams

Head of Scientific Development Department

2014 - 2022

Central Forensic Laboratory of the Police

- Implemented policies for project completions and employee responsibilities
- Responsible for developing and implementing project portfolio management processes.
- Supervised project document workflow.
- Communicated with various entities involved in the project.
- Oversaw the team of 35+ project managers at CFLP
- Responsible for the creation and implementation of the CFLP R&D strategy

Specialist, forensic expert

2003 - 2014

Central Forensic Laboratory of the Police

- Carrying out forensic genetics opinions
- Developing and implementing new forensic methods and software tools (LIMS)

CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAININGS

- Intro to Javascript Code First Girls (in progress)
- Intro to HTML and CSS Udacity
- Javascript girsl.js
- Agile with Atlassian Jira
- · Certified Project Management Associate (IPMA-D)
- Negotiations Kozminsky University
- Role of manager in coaching

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.